♪♪♪
♪ WE COME ON THE SLOOP JOHN B ♪
♪ MY GRANDFATHER AND ME ♪
♪ AROUND NASSAU TOWN
WE DID ROAM ♪
♪ DRINKIN' ALL NIGHT ♪
♪ GOT INTO A FIGHT ♪
♪ WELL, I FEEL SO BROKE UP,
I WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪♪♪
♪ SO HOIST UP
THE JOHN B'S SAIL ♪
♪ SEE HOW THE MAINSAIL SETS ♪
♪ CALL FOR THE CAPTAIN ASHORE,
LET ME GO HOME ♪
♪ LET ME GO HOME ♪
♪ I WANNA GO HOME, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ WELL, I FEEL SO BROKE UP,
I WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ DO, DO, DO, DO, DO,
DO, DO, DO, DO, DO, DO ♪
♪ THE FIRST MATE, HE GOT DRUNK ♪
♪ AND BROKE
IN THE CAPTAIN'S TRUNK ♪
♪ THE CONSTABLE HAD
TO COME AND TAKE HIM AWAY ♪
♪ SHERIFF JOHN STONE (AH) ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE ME ALONE,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ WELL, I FEEL SO BROKE UP,
I WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪♪♪
♪ SO HOIST UP
THE JOHN B'S SAIL
(HOIST UP THE JOHN B'S) ♪
♪ SEE HOW THE MAINSAIL SETS
(SEE HOW THE MAINSAIL) ♪
♪ CALL FOR THE CAPTAIN ASHORE,
LET ME GO HOME ♪
♪ LET ME GO HOME,
WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ LET ME GO HOME ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET ME GO HOME
(HOIST UP THE JOHN B'S SAIL) ♪
♪ HOIST UP THE JOHN B'S SAIL
(HOIST UP THE JOHN B'S) ♪
♪ I FEEL SO BROKE UP,
I WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ LET ME GO HOME
(THE JOHN B'S SAIL) ♪
♪ POOR COOK,
HE CAUGHT THE FITS ♪
♪ AND THREW AWAY ALL MY GRITS ♪
♪ AND THEN HE TOOK
AND HE ATE UP ALL OF MY CORN ♪
♪ LET ME GO HOME (AH) ♪
♪ WHY DON'T THEY LET ME
GO HOME ♪
♪ THIS IS THE WORST TRIP
I'VE EVER BEEN ON ♪
♪♪♪
♪ SO HOIST UP
THE JOHN B'S SAIL ♪
♪ HOIST UP THE JOHN B'S ♪
♪ SEE HOW THE MAINSAIL
(SEE HOW THE MAINSAIL) ♪
♪ CALL FOR THE CAPTAIN ASHORE ♪
♪ LET ME GO HOME
(LET ME GO HOME) ♪
♪ I WANNA GO HOME